export const HypotenuseMessage = "The length of hypotenuse is  ";
export const calculateAreaErrorMsg = "Enter valid side lengths such that each side lengths";
export const calculateAreaResultMsg = "Area of a triangle using heron's formula is "
export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
        answerList: ["45°", "90°", "60°"],
        answer: ["90°"]
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
        answerList: ["obtuse", "acute", "right angled"],
        answer: ["right angled"]
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "A triangle can have",
        answerList: ["one right angle", "two right angles"],
        answer: ["one right angle"]
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which of the following can form a right angled triangle?",
        answerList: ["14, 15, 26", "12, 16, 20"],
        answer: ["14, 15, 26"]
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which of the following triangles are always similar?",
        answerList: ["Equilateral triangle", "Isosceles triangle"],
        answer: ["Equilateral triangle"]
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "If one angle of a triangle is obtuse, then which one of the following is the possible measure of remaining angles?",
        answerList: ["100°", "85°"],
        answer: ["85°"]
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "The perimeter of scalene triangle with sides a, b, c is",
        answerList: ["a + b + c", "2a", "None of these"],
        answer: ["a + b + c"]
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "A scalene triangle has ___ lines of symmetry",
        answerList: ["two", "no", "15"],
        answer: ["no"]
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "A triangle can have",
        answerList: ["one right angle", "two right angles"],
        answer: ["one right angle"]
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "There is a right triangle PQR where: angle Q = 90°; angle P = angle R. What is the measure of angles P and R?",
        answerList: ["85°", "65°", "45°"],
        answer: ["45°"]
    },
]